<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days</string>
    <string name="tip1">Drink a glass of water first thing in the morning</string>
    <string name="tip2">Take the stairs</string>
    <string name="tip3">Make half your plate veggies</string>
    <string name="tip4">Get a fitness tracker + track your steps</string>
    <string name="tip5">Switch to non-toxic household cleaning products</string>
    <string name="tip6">Use non-toxic skincare + personal care products</string>
    <string name="tip7">Take a probiotic daily</string>
    <string name="tip8">Eat real food</string>
    <string name="tip9">Stand up every 30 minutes while working</string>
    <string name="tip10">Get sunlight every day</string>
    <string name="tip11">Fill your home with houseplants</string>
    <string name="tip12">Sweat every day</string>
    <string name="tip13">Have a daily green smoothie</string>
    <string name="tip14">Work hard + be kind</string>
    <string name="tip15">Cultivate a positive mindset</string>
    <string name="tip16">Get enough sleep</string>
    <string name="tip17">Start your day with a healthy morning routine</string>
    <string name="tip18">Eat the rainbow</string>
    <string name="tip19">Floss your teeth</string>
    <string name="tip20">Spend time alone</string>
    <string name="tip21">Do things you enjoy</string>
    <string name="tip22">Choose organic foods when possible</string>
    <string name="tip23">A teaspoon of apple cider vinegar keeps the doctor away</string>
    <string name="tip24">Smile often</string>
    <string name="tip25">Work on overcoming your fears</string>
    <string name="tip26">Use a yoga ball as a desk chair</string>
    <string name="tip27">Manage stress with self-care activities</string>
    <string name="tip28">Intermittent fasting can promote weight loss</string>
    <string name="tip29">Drink a glass of water after every alcoholic beverage</string>
    <string name="tip30">Practice gratitude</string>
    
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30</string>

    <string name="instruction1">Coffee’s great too, but it’s best to start your day by re-hydrating with a full glass of water.
        Hydrating first thing in the morning helps to aid digestion, enhance skin health and boost energy.</string>
    <string name="instruction2">Taking the stairs instead of the elevator is a simple way to get a little more physical activity in your daily life.
        It also strengthens and tones your legs and core while you’re at it!</string>
    <string name="instruction3">A simple hack for healthy eating (and portion control) is to make half your plate veggies at each meal.</string>
    <string name="instruction4">Using a fitness tracker to track your steps is an easy way to make sure you’re getting enough physical activity each day.</string>
    <string name="instruction5">Conventional household cleaning products are full of harmful chemical ingredients that are not good for our health (or the health of our kids or pets!). </string>
    <string name="instruction6">Similar to cleaning products, conventional skincare and personal care products are formulated with toxic ingredients we should not regularly let absorb into our body’s largest organ.</string>
    <string name="instruction7">Maintaining a healthy gut has significant impacts on digestion, skin health, immunity, mental health and more.</string>
    <string name="instruction8">Aim to eat real food that’s made of whole food ingredients you would have in your own kitchen pantry, or that your grandmother would recognize. </string>
    <string name="instruction9">Reduce the harmful effects of sitting (like at your desk job) by standing up and moving around for a minute or two every half hour.</string>
    <string name="instruction10">Vitamin D is one of the most important nutrients for overall health, and sunlight is one of our best sources of it.</string>
    <string name="instruction11">Houseplants help to cleanse your indoor air (sadly, it probably needs it!), they’re pretty, and research even shows they improve mood, creativity and problem solving!</string>
    <string name="instruction12">Aim to sweat in some way each day—whether that’s via running, biking, dancing, hot yoga, or any other physical activity you enjoy. </string>
    <string name="instruction13">Green smoothies as a snack or simple, on-the-go breakfast are an easy way to get your greens in each day.</string>
    <string name="instruction14">Enough said!</string>
    <string name="instruction15">“The only difference between a good day and a bad day is your attitude.” It’s true—mindset is everything!</string>
    <string name="instruction16">Most adults need 7-9 hours of sleep each night. But in addition to quantity, quality of sleep matters too!</string>
    <string name="instruction17">Start each day with fulfilling activities that set the tone for how you want to feel—whether that’s inspired, relaxed, productive, or something else.</string>
    <string name="instruction18">Aim to eat all the colors of the rainbow each day. (Natural colors only, no Skittles!)</string>
    <string name="instruction19">Floss your teeth daily for good dental health and overall health.
        Not only does flossing daily protect your teeth and gums, but good dental health is also important for immunity and heart health.</string>
    <string name="instruction20">Spending regular time alone helps to get to know and stay in touch with yourself (we’re all constantly growing and changing!).</string>
    <string name="instruction21">This often gets overlooked as an essential element of healthy living—doing things each day that you enjoy!</string>
    <string name="instruction22">There are a gazillion health, environmental and social reasons to choose organic foods.</string>
    <string name="instruction23">Apple cider vinegar cures everything (well… almost everything!). </string>
    <string name="instruction24">Smiling boosts your physical and mental health (it’s true!), so find ways to smile as often as you can throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="instruction25">Fears hold us back and keep us from living life as our best self. Acknowledge your fears and take steps to overcome them.</string>
    <string name="instruction26">Save your back/shoulders/neck and strengthen your core by using a yoga ball as a desk chair.</string>
    <string name="instruction27">Chronic stress is detrimental to both your physical and mental health. </string>
    <string name="instruction28">We’re not really into dieting (restrictions are no fun!), but intermittent fasting is more of an eating pattern than a diet.</string>
    <string name="instruction29">Nope, we’re not going to tell you to refrain from alcohol (though you certainly can if you want!).</string>
    <string name="instruction30">Practice gratitude each day—this could be when you wake up, before bed, or during your lunch break at work.</string>
</resources>